Now, the switch statement here is testing whether the spice level
statement switch ini menguji apakah variabel bilangan bulat
integer variable is equal to a list of possible values.
spice level setara dengan daftar kemungkinan nilai.
If the spice level is 0, let's go ahead and step through the code,
Jika spice level 0, mari lanjutkan dan periksa kode,
which means it doesn't equal 1, it doesn't equal 2 or 3 or 4.
yang artinya tidak sama dengan 1, tidak setara dengan 2, 3, atau 4.
So we can skip these cases and
Jadi kita bisa melewatkan case-case ini dan
that means it's going to fall into the default case.
langsung ke case default.
So we set the flavor to be not spicy.
Jadi kita atur flavor menjadi not spicy.
Now what happens when the spice level is 2?
Apa yang terjadi jika spice level-nya 2?
That means it doesn't evaluate in the first case for 1, so
Artinya bahwa statement tidak mengevaluasi case pertama untuk 1, jadi
we skip that case but it does equal 2.
kita lewatkan case itu tapi sama dengan 2.
So it falls into the second case which sets the flavor string to be medium,
Maka masuk ke case kedua yang mengatur string flavor sebagai medium,
all right.
oke.
Now this case is interesting.
Case ini menarik.
What happens when the spice level is 3?
Apa yang terjadi jika spice level 3?
Now, looking into our code, we fall into case 3 and we set the flavor to be hot.
Melihat kode kita, kita masuk ke case 3 dan mengatur flavor menjadi hot.
But there's no break statement.
Tapi tidak ada statementt break.
So we're actually going to fall into the 4th case,
Jadi sebenarnya kita akan masuk ke case keempat,
which sets the flavor string to very hot.
yang mengatur string flavor sebagai very hot.
Now that just means we just overrode the flavor variable with a new value.
Artinya, kita telah menimpa variabel flavor dengan nilai baru.
Then we hit a break statement, which will execute our switch statement.
Lalu kita tiba di stetemen break, yang akan menjalankan statementt switch kita.
So the latest value of the flavor string when we exit the switch statement
Maka nilai terbaru untuk string flavor saat kita mengeluarkan statement switch
is actually very hot.
sebenarnya adalah very hot.
The last few cases are fairly straightforward.
Beberapa case terakhir cukup langsung.
For a spiceLevel of 1, the flavor is going to be mild.
Untuk spiceLevel 1, flavor-nya menjadi lembut.
For a spiceLevel of 4, the flavor is also going to be very hot.
Untuk spiceLevel 4, flavor-nya juga menjadi very hot.
And then lastly, for a spiceLevel of 10, there is no explicit case.
Dan terakhir, untuk spice level 10, tidak ada case yang eksplisit.
So we fall into the default case again, and that flavor is not spicy.
Jadi kita masuk ke case default lagi, dan flavor itu adalah not spicy.
Great work.
Kerja bagus.
Hope you got some good practice in,
Semoga Anda banyak berlatih,
and feel more comfortable with switch statements.
dan merasa nyaman dengan statement switch.